Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art buildings and grounds records, 1870-2007 COR0007.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative records, Series 13
  - Financial records, Series 13 subseries 2
    - Corcoran- Tax Exempt Status, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 60)
    - Real Estate, Donohue, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 61)
    - Archive, Records/Forms, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 62)
    - Policy, Employee Benefit, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 63)
    - Policy, Mail Services, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 64)
    - Policy, Manual CK Req., circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 65)
    - Policy, Revise PO System, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 66)
    - Policy, TIAA CR-Accum W/D, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 67)
    - Tax, Claim to Tx Credit, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 68)
    - Tax, Receipt/Mineral Cty., circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 69)
    - Tax, Exempt Form/AT&T, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 70)
    - Tax, Property/1680 Wisc. Ave., circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 71)
    - Tax, Exempt Prop. Use Report, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 72)
    - Adm/Bldg Proj/Lansburg Bldg, 901 F Street NW Smith Braidon Co., circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 73)
    - Lease- Wisconsin Avenue, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 74)
    - New Postal Systems, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 75)
    - New Postal Systems (Research), circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 76)
    - Adm/Bldg Proj/Atec/Asbestos Abatement Ceramic Reloc, 1990; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 77)
    - Adm/Bldg Proj/Dormitory Repairs/(Misc.), 1990; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 78)
    - Adm/Bldg Proj/A-Z Restoration, Inc. Flat Roof Repairs, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 79)
    - Certif., Exempt/DC Sales & Tx, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 80)
    - Certif., Exempt/Fed Income Tx, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 81)
    - Corcoran Ball, 2008; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Gehry Contract, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Corcoran: The Children's Center for Art and Technology, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Randall School Mixed-Use Project, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Corcoran: Architectural Press, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - January Board Meeting, 2001; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Finanical Responsibility Regulation, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Trailer for G-Town, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Harassment Question, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - RFK Legal Issue, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - ASCAP, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Check Theft, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Curatorial- Lewis, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Neri, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Line of Credit- PNC, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - PNC- Randall Loan, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Legal & Consulting Fees, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Amended & Restated Line of Credit between PNC Bank, National Association, and the Trustees of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2006; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - IT, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - CFO Search, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - HR-Old TIAA CERF, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Second Sheet Bond Paper, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Staff-HR-Parking, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Survey Responses, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - HR, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Hiring Process Draft Forms/Documents, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Shop Data, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Benefits, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Performance, 2000; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Self Study Report Appendices A-Q, 2002 July 1; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - DCAD, 2009; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folders 2-4)
    - Self Study Report Appendices I-IV, 2002 July; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Self Study Report Appendices I-IV, 2002 July; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Self Study Report, 2002 July; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Condition Assessment Mechancial and Electrical Systems, 1995 May 17; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Design Development Budget Corcoran Gallery of Art Renovation and Addition Gehry Partners, LLP, 20002 July 16; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Material List/Building Systems Schematic Design in Progress, 2001 May 25; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Material List/Building Systems Schematic Design in Progress Volume 2, 2001 May 25; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Material List/Building Systems Schematic Design, 2001 November 16; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2005 June 28; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folders 1-3)
    - Executive Committee, 2002 February 25; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2005 September 20; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2006 September 25-26; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2006 December 11; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Board of Trustees Special Meeting, 2006 October 23; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Update and Request for Approval of the Attached Resolutions, 2006 July 6; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2006 January 30; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Strategic Partnerships, 2006 October 26; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 February 13; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 April 23; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 June 18; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Misc. Articles, Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2008 September 24; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2008 January 28; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2008 September 22; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Audit, 1974; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Audit, 1975; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Audit, 1977; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Audit, 1978; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Audit, 1979; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Audit, 1980; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Audit, 1981; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Audit, 1982; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Audit, 1983; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Audit, 1984; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Audit, 1985; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Audit, 1986; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Audit, 1987; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Audit, 1988; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Audit, 1989; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Audit, 1990; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Audit, 1991; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Audit, 1992; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Audit, 1993; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Audit, 1994; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Audit, 1995; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Audit, 1996; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Audit, 1997; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Audit, 1998; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Audit, 1999; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Audit, 2000; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Audit, 2003; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Audit, 2004; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Audit, 2006; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Audit, 2007; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - Audit, 2008; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Expense by Category-, 1998; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax- Public Disclosure Copy, circa 1990s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Report to Management, 1997; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Presentation to the Finance Committee, 1998; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Finance Statement for the years ended Report Thereon, 1997-1998; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Trustees of the Corcoran Gallery of Art Report on Federal Financial Assistance in Arccordance with OMB Circular A-133, 1997; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Report to Management, 1999; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Report to Management, 1999; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Consolidation Financial Statements for the years, 1999-2000; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Trustees of the Corcoran Gallery of Art Report on Federal Financial Assistance in Accordance with OMB Circular A-133, 2000; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Report to Management, 2000; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Finance Committee & Investments Subcommittee Meetings, 2001-2003; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Consolidation Financial Statements, 2000-2001; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Report to Management, 2001; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - The Corcoran Finance Committee Presentation, 2002; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Meeting of the Finance Committee, 2002; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Finance Committee & Investments Subcommittee Meetings, 2002-2004; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Consolidated Finance Statements, 2002-2003; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Price Waterhouse Coopers, Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Consolidation Financial Statements, 2001-2002; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Investment Subcommittee Meeting, 2002-2003; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Financial Committee Minutes, 2002; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Finance Committee Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2003; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Price Waterhouse Coopers The Corcoran Gallery of Art Audit Committee Report Resolution and Completion, 2003; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Price Waterhouse Coopers Trustees of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2003; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Investment Subcommittee, 2003; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Price Waterhouse Coopers Trustees of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2004; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - FC, 1992 October 15; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - IC, 1992 October 22; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - FC, 1992 November 12; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - FC, 1992 December 10; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - FC, 1993 January 7; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - IC, 1993 January 28; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - FC, 1993 March 11; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - FC, 1993 April 18; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - IC, 1993 April 29; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - FC, 1993 May 6; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - FC, 1993 June 10; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - FC, 1993 June 15; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - FC, 1993 August 19; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - IC, 1993 October 14; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - FC, 1993 October 21; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - FC, 1992 November 12; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - FC, 1993 December 9; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - FC, 1994 January 14; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - IC, 1993 January 27; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - FC, 1994 February 10; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - FC, 1994 March 17; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - FC, 1994 April 12; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - IC, 1994 April 28; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - IC, 1994 May 11; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - FC, 1994 May 19; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - FC, 1994 June 16; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - IC, 1994 June 30; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - FC, 1994 July 21; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - IC, 1994 August 1; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - IC, 1994 August 8; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - FC, 1994 August 25; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - IC, 1994 September 15; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - FC, 1994 September 22; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - FC, 1994 October 20; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - IC, 1994 October 26; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - FC, 1994 November 17; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 38)
    - FC, 1994 December 15; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 39)
    - FC, 1995 January 26; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 40)
    - IC, 1995 January 26; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 41)
    - FC, 1995 March 23; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 42)
    - IC, 1995 April 17; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 43)
    - FC, 1995 May 19; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 44)
    - FC, 1995 June 23; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 45)
    - IC, 1995 July 17; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 46)
    - FC, 1994 August 24; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 47)
    - FC, 1995 September 21; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 48)
    - IC, 1995 October 13; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 49)
    - FC, 1995 October 26; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 50)
    - Current Finance Committee, 1996-1997; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 51)
    - Current Investment Management Committee, 1996-1997; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 52)
    - FC, 1995 November 17; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 53)
    - FC, 1995 December 21; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 54)
    - FC, 1996 January 22; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 55)
    - IC, 1996 February 1; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 56)
    - FC, 1996 March 21; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 57)
    - IC, 1996 April 15; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 58)
    - FC, 1996 April 22; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 59)
    - FC, 1996 May 17; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 60)
    - FC, 1996 June 15; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 61)
    - FC, 1996 July 10; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 62)
    - IC, 1996 July 16; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 63)
    - FC, 1996 August 20; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 64)
    - FC, 1996 September 18; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 65)
    - FC, 1996 October 21; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 66)
    - IC, 1996 October 24; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 67)
    - FC, 1996 November 15; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 68)
    - IC, 1997 January 21; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 69)
    - FC, 1997 January 24; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 70)
    - FC, 1997 February 20; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 71)
    - FC, 1997 March 19; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 72)
    - IC, 1997 April 23; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 73)
    - FC, 1997 May 15; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 74)
    - FC, 1997 June 19; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 75)
    - FC, 1997 July 24; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 76)
    - FC, 1997 July 31; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 77)
    - FC, 1997 August; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 78)
    - FC, 1997 September 19; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 79)
    - FC, 1997 September 9; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 80)
    - IC, 1997 October 29; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 81)
    - Building & Grounds Committee Meeting Notes, 1992-1993; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 75, Folder 82)
    - College - Housing, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - College - Programs, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - College - Issues, 1999 Dec 22; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - College - Enrollment, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - College - Faculty, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - College - Certification Audits, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - College - Staff Positions, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Inclement Weather School Codes - Closing, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Museum - Marketing, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Contributed Revenue, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Museum - Shop - FYE Sales, 2004 Jun - 2008 Nov; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folders 11-13)
    - Strategic Planning - Values, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Cafe, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Strategic Planning - College, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Financial Ratios, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Strategic Planning - Economic Impact, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Process Planning, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Security Facilities, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Renovation - Safety, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Front Door Renovation, 2000 June 7; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Renovation - Storage, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Space Survey, 1999; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Facility - Fire Report, 2004; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Renovations - Costs, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Renovation Budget & Report, 1996; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - ATX Long Distance Telephone, 2000 Feb; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - ADA Compliance, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Sq Footage, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Floor Plans, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 31)
    - Museum - Staff Evaluations, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 32)
    - Revies FI/02, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 33)
    - Staff Positions - Dev, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 34)
    - Financial Budget, 2004; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 35)
    - Financial - Prior FY Reports Monthly, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 36)
    - Celebration of Life - Albert Uster and Leonard B. "Bud" Doggett, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 37)
    - Property Tax Docs, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 38)
    - DNC Wire Info, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 39)
    - Purchase Procedure Accounting, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 40)
    - Accounting Procedures, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 41)
    - Finance Policy, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 42)
    - Reusch International, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 43)
    - Audit Planning, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 44)
    - Independent Contractor Rules Accounting Procedures, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 45)
    - Finance - Tax Exempt Funding, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 46)
    - Chart of Accounts, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 47)
  - General administrative files, Series 13 subseries 3
    - P Street Proposal, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Plate Glass, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Cafe, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Cafe Contract, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Food Services, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Cafe de Paris Contract, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Golden Temple Food Proposal, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Food Services: Gallery & School, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Exhibitions Turned Down Admin-PCM, 1977-1980; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Admin Exhibition Proposals, 1977-1980; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Trustees of Corcoran Gallery of Art Audit Committee Manual, 1978 October; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Proposals to Provide Professional Services to the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1978; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Archives, 1978-1980; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Building & Grounds, 1978; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Building & Grounds, 1977; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Chronological File- Personnel, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Planning Committee, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Assoc. of Art Museum Directors, 1977-1978; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Assoc. of Art Museum Directors, 1979-1980; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Corcoran Archives Information Sent to Archives for Storage, 1984 August; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 10-71-5104 Legal, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 10-90 Insurance, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - New York Avenue Building Project, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - ADM. Blue Copies of Purchase Orders, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Contract Information File, 1988; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)